naharnet.com 2011-06-23

# Naharnet - Privacy Policy

Naharnet takes seriously the issue of safeguarding your privacy online. At the same time as Naharnet is committed to bringing you information tailored to your individual needs, we recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about you. In adopting this member privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using information against your reasonable expectations of privacy. 

Please read the following statement to understand our views and practices regarding this matter and how they pertain to you as you make full use of our many offerings: 

Naharnet does not collect personally identifying information about individuals, except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. 

For each Member of Naharnet, our web servers automatically collect information about which pages are visited. This information is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for traffic audits. We also provide this information on an aggregated anonymous basis to our advertisers. 

Naharnet places a "cookie" on the browser of a Member's computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. A cookie is used to tell when your computer has contacted us; we use this information for editorial purposes and for other purposes such as the navigation from one module to the other. If you disable the cookie of your browser, you cannot access Naharnet.
